Hello friends, welcome to our
[music],
we will tell you everything in this video, so friends, do
not skip the video at all,
watch till the end and if you have
not subscribed to our channel, then please do subscribe to the channel as well, so let's take
you to the video, let's
look at the bike,
what parts of the bike are damaged, let's
see everything and also see which parts have been repaired, so
first of all this front indicator, that is, the
sketch here also and here also this light is broken
completely here and this
indicator and this clutch lever, that is, it has become crooked, in this
way there is damage here as well
and here on the leg guard also
it is worn out more than half, it got worn out here and on the
brake
also a little bit the brake got worn out here and the
rest of this lead fatest is also worn out and the
indicators on the rear side are also broken, in
this way the accident of the bike on both this and this side was at a
very high speed, at a
speed of about 10810 and it has fallen, it has
fallen very fast  From this side also, a little
sketch came here and here also it has
a broken brake pedal, so let's see
which parts get repaired
and what is the process, in how many days the
bike is received, so today we will go to deposit
this bike, today's date is
17222, that is, we will go on the 17th, so let's see in
how many days the
bike gets repaired, so friends, do
not skip the video at all, watch till the end only and now let's
talk about the documents,
what documents are required in making the file and submitting it,
there for insurance, first of all
Aadhar card and then secondly
registration, then driver's license and
photo copy of the bank i.e. passbook so that the
money can be received in the return and the statement of the
parts and the policy will be of the
insurance policy, so a photo copy of the passbook
is required so that first you will have to
deposit the money in cash and then after this the
return will be credited to your account, so
this is how it is done
friends, this vehicle is coming
and now it will be deposited here and we will
get this card, so today we deposit it  Let's see the
bike and see
in
how many days it takes to get it after repair, the
card will be made for us now, we will write
its name, so here brother is writing the Chas number, Chas
and
serial Chas
number, we will give this card to us and then we will see
in how many days our bike reaches us,
so from here we have received this receipt, the
date is written on it and Apache
white color, that is, the color number of the bike and on this
side
also the bike has been deposited here, now we are going
home, we will come when they call, then we will
come to collect our bike from here, so
friends we have come to collect our bike,
this is our bike coming in front, let's
see which parts of it have been changed and
which have not been changed, let's
show which parts of the bike have been
changed, so first of all let's
talk about the guiser, the
guiser has not been changed because there were
not so many scratches on it and the side panels of
both the sides have been changed, this one and this one
and the light has also changed, it had got worn out a bit, so
this has also been replaced and the indicator
indicator was placed near one side but
we did not place it on one side  Got it installed
and here another clutch lever was also installed
and the pedal bar as well as the handle bar, both were installed, one on this side
and the other on this side, and here
this also got changed, it was
completely worn out, this was also changed, the
rest was not changed here, they did not pass this
here
and the rear side, the rear side, the internal gutters were broken,
both of them were installed, so new ones were installed, so
now friends, let me show you the bill for
this, whether the bill for this has come, so
these are the old parts, whatever has been
replaced, new ones have been installed, these are the old bikes, we will take them
home, the
lock guard and this is our light, head lamp,
head lamp and this handle bar, rain bar,
indicator visor,
we will take all the stuff home, so
friends, in this way you can claim for your bike
or any other vehicle
and this is the process in it,
you will have to submit all the documents in the insurance office from the
company from where you got the insurance done,
and then the
money that will come in your refund, it will take
time for you, that is, 15 to 20  It
may take a day for that money to come, so friends, do
tell me how you liked this information by commenting and if you have already
subscribed to us, then this is all in this video, you will get to see us
in some next video with some next topic, till then
bye to all friends, friends, do
use helmet while driving.